Finding Aid for Citizens for Education (Grosse Pointe, Mich.) records, 1968-1975
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Citizens for Education (Grosse Pointe, Mich.) records 1968-1975
Citizens for Education (Grosse Pointe, Mich.).
1 linear foot
85178 Bi 2
Grosse Pointe, Michigan, citizens group concerned with problems and goals of their public school system; organizational records.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was the gift of Robert W. Bradley for the organization (donor no. 6490 ) and came to the library in 1980.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Citizens for Education was a Grosse Pointe, Michigan, citizens group concerned with problems and goals of their public school system. The organization flourished in the period of the late 1960s and early to mid-1970s.
The record group consists of constitution and by-laws, minutes of the board of directors, financial material, and correspondence and other papers concerning organizational programs and school board elections.
Subjects:
Citizens' associations--Michigan--Grosse Pointe.; Education--Michigan--Grosse Pointe.; Grosse Pointe (Mich.).; Schools--Michigan--Grosse Pointe.
- Organizational records
  - Constitution and by-laws (Box 1)
  - Annual reports (Box 1)
  - Lists of Board of Directors (Box 1)
  - Lists of members (Box 1)
  - Minutes
    - 1968-1970 (Box 1)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters (Box 1)
  - Clippings (Box 1)
  - Financial records (Box 1)
  - Papers
    - Undated (Box 1)
    - 1968 (Box 1)
    - 1969 (Box 1)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 1)
    - 1972 (Box 1)
    - 1973 (Box 1)
    - 1974 (Box 1)
    - 1975 (Box 1)